<Document>
  # Rule 11: Follow Powergaming Guidelines
  ## 11A. General Powergaming Guidelines
    - Don't rush for or prepare equipment unrelated to your job for no purpose other than to have it "just in case" (referred to as "Powergaming").
        [color=#ffe59d]* Finding something laying around without a clear owner is a generally a valid reason, this mainly applies to maintenance items. 
        * If you are concerned as to whether or not what you're allowed to go for, feel free to ahelp and ask an admin.[/color]
        [color=#ff0000] Lack of administrator response does not constitute approval.[/color]

    - A medical doctor does not need insulated gloves gamestart, and the Head of Personnel does not need to give themselves armory access so they can go grab a gun. Have an actual reason for needing these things.

    - Don't manufacture weapons, bombs, or deadly poisons before you know of any reason you would need them.

    - Don't preemptively hide antagonist objectives or preemptively secure them with higher security than normally required.

  ## 11B. Role-Specific Powergaming Guidelines
    - Security of antagonist objective items:
        [color=#ffe59d]* Hiding antagonist objective items or preemptively securing them with higher security than usually required or than would make logical sense violates our powergaming and roleplay guidelines.
        * If you acquire an antagonist objective item in a non-Standard approved manner, you should try and return it to its rightful owner. If this is not possible you should try and secure it to the best of your abilities. You may coordinate with other crew to achieve this goal.[/color]
    
    [color=#8a6740]Logistics Gameplay Guidelines:[/color]
      [color=#ffe59d]* Salvage should not hoard items and weapons unless there is a critical situation on the station that calls for it. Failure to comply with this will result in a roleban. See example considerations below.
        * Salvage shouldn't have a weaponpile comparable to the Station Armory, coordinate with Logistics to give these to Security.
        * Salvage shouldn't hoard materials and should put effort into moving materials back to Logistics.
        * Salvage shouldn't hoard items that other departments are in demand of (Chemvends, exotic seeds, etc.) without permission from that department.
        * If you are unsure what you are allows to keep and not allowed to keep, ask via aHelp.
      * Salvage is HIGHLY ENCOURAGED to use fulton beacons and fultons to transfer goods from the Reclaimer back to the station.
      * The Reclaimer is free to be edited as Salvage (with LO approval) wishes to see fit.
      * Some leeway to powergaming as Salvage is given if you are actively contributing to the station, so long as it does not violate the aforementioned Powergaming Guidelines.

      * As LO and Cargo Technicians, put some effort into ensuring items get to their respective entities. See example considerations below.
        * Notify over radio that a supply request for the respective department/individual arrived.
        * Deliver the supplies to the respective department/individual.[/color]
    
    [color=#cd76d3]Epistemics Gameplay Guidelines:[/color]
      [color=#ffe59d]* Don't ask borgs to rob all of Logistics' supplies, there are other departments that demand supplies as well. If you are a non-emagged borg and someone asks you to do this aHelp it.
      * Borging should always be saved in case someone's body is gibbed or unless they request otherwise with proper documentation.[/color]
</Document>