<Document>
  # Rule 12: Security and command roles are held to a higher standard and must follow space law.
  ## 12A. Command and Security Standards
    - Security, Justice, and Command roles are held to a higher standard of roleplay, and are expected to know and perform their jobs to the best of their ability. These roles often heavily impact the round and require more careful and conscientious roleplay; if you cannot meet these requirements do not take these roles.
      [color=#ffe59d]* These three departments are required to read and follow Grimbly Station Space Law, Standard Operating Procedure, Alert Procedure, and Company Policy to the best of their ability.[/color]

    - Abandoning your role to go do whatever you want instead of managing your department or maintaining security, abusing your position or using it to make arbitrary or malicious choices to the detriment of the station, and being negligent to the point of harm is prohibited.
    
    - Be competent in your job and department. Failure to know the basics of your department is liable to result in a job ban.
        [color=#ffe59d]* A CMO should know basic chemistry and treatment.
        * An LO should know basic money management, shuttle piloting, mailing, and Salvage procedures.
        * An HoS should know Space Law, Brig timers, considerations of criminal cases, etc.
        * A Captain should know how to delegate jobs, the basics of each department, and how to handle conflicts.
        * An HoP should know how to do basic service roles, job assignment, and ID permission considerations on a case-by-case basis.
        * A MG should know how to do xenoarcheology, anomaly management, and psionic/glimmer management.
        * A CE should know how to repair, basic atmos distro setup, and setup power.[/color]

    - As Command and Security are more RP intensive than other departments, communication is essential to these roles. Failure to communicate with others is liable to result in a job ban.

    - Uphold the Law and maintain order. Do not engage in lawbreaking activity or troublemaker behavior. Security is expected to intervene into criminal activity where possible. Heads of Staff are at minimum expected to report criminal activity to Security.

    - Command members besides the Logistics Officer are not permitted to leave the station on salvage expeditions.

  ## 12B. Chronological Considerations
    - If you don’t have time to play a full round, do not select these roles.
    - If you need to leave your computer temporarily, send an ahelp or notify your fellow crew via the radio.
    - If you need to leave the round, notify your fellow crew via departmental radio, notify the admins via aHelp, and put your equipment in its respective secure containment prior to going to cryo.
      [color=#ffe59d]* If you need to leave IMMEDIATELY, please at least send an ahelp saying that you're leaving so we can notify your peers accordingly.[/color]

  ## 12C. Roleplay-Gameplay Standards
    - Security and Command roles are forbidden from using a syndicate uplink to receive contraband without written permission from Central Command.
    - Do not hire random crew to be your bodyguards or promote random crewmember to Captain or a Head of Staff at random. If you need bodyguards, talk to your security department. If you need a new Command role, talk to the personnel in that related department.
    - Do not abandon the station during Nuclear Operatives. You are supposed to protect the station, not let operatives kill everyone on it without a fight.
</Document>