<Document>
  [color=#fcff00]# Rule 2: Follow the server expectations[/color]
 
  [color=#ff6e00]## 2A. Gameplay Expectations[/color]
    - Do not cheat.

    - Do not abuse glitches and exploits.[color=#ff0000]We have zero tolerance for abusing exploits/bugs. If you’re not sure, ask an admin.[/color] Otherwise, please use the #bug-reports channel on the Discord to report the bug.

    - THE USAGE OF ANY THIRD-PARTY APPLICATIONS/SCRIPTS/CLIENT MODIFICATIONS TO GAIN AN ADVANTAGE, AVOID INTENDED GAME/SERVER MECHANICS, OR TO HARM SERVER INFRASTRUCTURE IS STRICTLY PROHIBITED. ANY AND ALL INSTANCES OF THIS WILL BE MET WITH AN APPEAL-ONLY BAN.

    - If you are banned from a role or department, you may not play that role. This includes seeking or accepting promotions into roles you are banned from.

    - Do not make yourself a major problem/annoyance/disruption for the crew while not being an antagonist (i.e. self-antagging).

    - Do not make yourself a major problem/annoyance/disruption for one specific crew member in a way that would actively detract from the other player's enjoyment of the shift.

    - Do not, as a crewmate, hide the nuclear fission explosive (i.e. "the nuke") in an impossible to see location.

    - Significant End-of-round grief (EORG) is not allowed. This includes attacking, destroying, polluting, and injuring without reason both *at* and *on the way to* Central Command.
    [color=#ffe59d]
      * This also extends to the following:
      * Neutral parties, such as space dragons or sentient artifacts activating harmful nodes.
      * Attempts to block the docking ports or ports leading into Central Command.
      * Explosives and strategies with capacity for high collateral damage should not be used on or around the evacuation shuttle after it arrives at the station.
    [/color]

    - Department strikes (ex: cargonia and any variation thereof), riots, cults, and any other type of similar largely disruptive behavior are strictly forbidden. These activities are generally antagonist-only and all players regardless of antagonist status must obtain admin Central Command permission before engaging in this behavior (you are extremely unlikely to get permission).
    
    - AFK (aka SSD) and catatonic players are considered to have the same rights as a conscious crewmate.[/color]

  [color=#ff6e00]## 2B. Ahelp Guidelines[/color]
    - Do not ignore the admin help relay or abuse it by flooding it with garbage, checking for admins before stating a problem (ex: "hello?", "any admins?"), using it as a chatroom, or sending messages of no substance. Hostility to administrators in the relay will result in your removal.
    
    - Intentionally disconnecting, responding with hostility, or refusing to respond when an admin privately messages you in-game will be met with an appeal-only ban.
    
    - All AHelp messages are relayed to the Grimbly Station Discord. If an admin is not online, aHelp it anyways!
    
    - If you have any questions about these rules, please use the admin help (ahelp) menu by hitting F1 in-game or clicking the “Ahelp” button in the lobby.
    
    - If you are playing a departmental role and have to leave for more than 20 minutes, please head to cryo or notify an admin of your absence. This is to prevent role-hogging by AFK players. Failure to do so may result in admin cryo, whereas repeat offenders may receive rolebans or tempbans based on severity.
</Document>