<Document>
  <font color="#fcff00"># Rule 3: Follow Chat Guidelines</color>
  <font color="#ff6e00">3A. Use English and Be respectful</font>
    - Use English as your primary method of communication within the game and Grimbly Station servers.
    
    - Do not spam.
    
    - Do not advertise.
    
    - Be respectful towards other players in LOOC and OOC channels, and avoid making others uncomfortable. This can range anywhere from starting arguments to personal attacks against others, depending on the context.
    
    - We have a zero tolerance policy for hate speech, discrimination, threats, harassment, and other forms of hateful/harmful behavior. Failure to comply with this rule will result in community removal.
    
    - No racist remarks towards in-game races/morphotypes/borgs (i.e. Simulated Racism), while you don’t have to like everybody, you should not be acting upon nor expressing your distaste for other races/morphotypes/borgs. Failure to comply will result in an appeal-only ban.
    
    - Do not excessively complain in Dead, LOOC, or OOC channels. This further extends to complaining about the current or prior round in the Grimbly Station discord. If you have an issue aHelp it or go to the help channel in the discord. Excessive complaining (also known as being an OOC baby) does not add to the experience for anyone and makes you liable to administrative action.

  <font color="#ff6e00">3B. Avoid FailRP Communication</font>
    - Do not use netspeak in character (i.e. btw, lmfao).

    - Do not use the Emotes channel to bypass an inability to speak. This includes examples like "motions for you to put parmesan THEN sauce on the spaghetti," "im friendly," and "huh weird looks like I can't type."

    - Use the LOOC and OOC channels properly. Don’t speak of in-character matters in those channels unless you’re asking questions related to in-game concepts.
      <font color="ffe59d">* DO NOT use in-character channels to bypass a lack of ability to use OOC/LOOC chats (e.g. "Huh, wonder where captain went? *OOC* He probably left to get dinner lol"). This will result in an immediate dewhitelist.</font>
</Document>