<Document>
  # Rule : Follow Metagaming guidelines
  ## 4A. Death Rules and New Life Rules
    - If you die and get revived, do not act on things you saw while you were dead.

    - If a player dies and is brought back by way of cloning or borgification, they forget the last five minutes leading up to their death and cannot describe who or what killed them.

    - Players that are revived by using a defibrillator can only recall vague details about their death, such as "Someone shot me" or "I was set ablaze" but they cannot recall details beyond that.

  ## 4B. Meta Behaviors
    - Do not engage in meta-communications. This includes using chat channels outside of what is available in-game to communicate with other players in the same game.

    - Players are allowed to have in-character relationships (friends, enemies, or otherwise), however they cannot be used as a reason to grant or deny things based exclusively on having a relationship with one another(i.e. Meta-Friending).

    - You are allowed to have knowledge of past experiences with someone else in prior shifts. This does not give you permission to hold a grudge against someone that results in you treating them differently in an unfair way (i.e. Meta-Grudging).

    - Antagonists in previous rounds must not be treated differently due to their prior antagonist status. Notwithstanding, confession of crimes committed in a prior shift are still admissible in court.

    - Do not "Antag Roll." This is the act of joining rounds for the purpose of seeing if you joined as an antagonist, and leaving soon after if not. Players who have a history of this behavior will have their whitelist revoked and/or face a ban.
    
    - Do not place players into cryosleep unless they have given consent to do so, they are fully catatonic, or they have been sentenced to preservative stasis. Always examine a character to double check if they are SSD or catatonic prior to placing them into cryosleep.[/color]
    
    [color=#ff0000]- Do not stream the current round to the Grimbly Station Discord.
    - Please report players who violate this rule.[/color]

</Document>