<Document>
  # Rule 7: Follow Roleplay Guidelines
  ## 7A. Character RP Guidelines
    - Treat your character as a separate entity from you, the player. Your character's actions, feelings, and knowledge in-game should be based solely on the character's experiences and not your own as the player. Low roleplay actions that have no regard for your character or the setting (Memes, silly copy paste spam IC) are not acceptable.
    
    - Low roleplay actions that have no regard for your character or little bearing on setting (such as memes, silly copy paste spam IC) are not acceptable. Your character is a worker aboard a space station and will be held accountable.
    
    - Character development can occur over rounds but each round is a soft-reset, meaning you can have previous shift experience but your character will never have died in the past.
    
    - Non-security personnel should not seek to kill or detain unrelated threats (i.e validhunting). Crew may neutralize threats when they present themselves or if they are relevant to the crew member in question.
      [color=#ffe59d]* Certain severe emergencies may make it reasonable for normal crew to defend themselves and their station, such as nuclear operatives, a zombie outbreak, space dragon attack, or other critical situation.[/color]

  ## 7B. Role Standard Guidelines
    - Command and Security will be held to a higher standard for roleplay. Failure to comply will result in rolebans.

    - By picking prisoner, you have chosen to RP as a prisoner.
      [color=#ffe59d]* You are still subject to the same rules regarding escalation. You should only seek to escape from the brig with good reasoning (e.g. abusive security personnel, badly damaged permanent brig, lack of parole consideration DESPITE good behavior, etc.) OR after a 30 minute grace period.
      * Escaping for no reason OR before the 30 minute grace period is considered a self-antagonistic activity.
      * If you are unsure whether your escape reason is valid, feel free to AHelp it first.[/color]
      [color=#ff0000]Lack of administrator response does not constitute approval.[/color]
</Document>