<Document>
  # Rule 9: Antagonist Guidelines
  ## 9A. Behavioral Guidelines
    - The damage antagonists cause should be roughly proportional to their objectives, and contribute towards achieving them in some way.
      - [color=#ffe59d]* Antagonists have leniency in regards to what they can and can’t do.  If you are concerned as to whether or not what you're about to do is allowed, feel free to ahelp and ask an admin.[/color]
      - [color=#ff0000]Lack of administrator response does not constitute approval[/color]

    - Antagonists exist not only as a role for your character but also as a game mechanic. Seek to push forward the round through your antagonistic actions, rather than grind it to halt in pursuit of your objectives.

    - Exploits, arrivals camping, unnecessary round extensions, and other extremely lame behavior are forbidden.

  ## 9B. Antagonist Roleplay Guidelines
    - Other antagonists are not necessarily your friends. Traitors, rat kings, and possibly even space dragons are free agents, but no one should be working together with xenomorphs or zombies.

    - Ghost roles have their own independent rules that must be followed. 
    [color=#ff0000]Breaking these rules can result in a ban, whitelist removal, or both.[/color]

    - As a non-sentient or partially-sentient antagonist, you are expected to have only a limited understanding of space stations and their mechanics.
      - [color=#ffe59d]* Slimes, zombies, spiders, etc. Should not be targeting the gravity generator or the AME, nor should they be unnecessarily spacing the station.[/color]
    
    - Antagonist roles fall under 1 of 3 categories:
      - [color=#ffe59d]* Sapient - Your character is humanoid. This applies to Space Ninjas, Nuclear Operatives, Syndicate Agents, etc. Space-Law and SoP gives you protections unless specifically stated otherwise.[/color]
      - [color=#ffe59d]* Sentient - Your character is nonhumanoid. This applies to Space Dragons, Rat Kings, and other complex non-humanoid ghost-role antagonists. Space-Law and SoP gives you less protections unless specifically stated otherwise.[/color]
      - [color=#ffe59d]* Nonsentient/Partially-sentient - As a non-sentient or partially-sentient antagonist, you are expected to have only a limited understanding of space stations and their mechanics. Slimes, zombies, spiders, etc. Should not be targeting the gravity generator or the AME, nor should they be unnecessarily spacing the station. [/color]
</Document>